[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is true about the sloths diet?", "correct_answer": "Sloths are omnivores.", "incorrect_answers": ["Sloths are carnivores.", "Sloths are autotrophic organisms.", "Sloths are herbivores."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors starred in the 2009 movie Angels  Demons?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicolas Cage", "Robert De Niro", "Dustin Hoffman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred in Stanley Kubricks 1980 psychological horror movie The Shining?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Dustin Hoffman", "Robert De Niro", "Christopher Walken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In L.A. Dragnet, which is a 2003 remake of the TV series Dragnet, detective Joe Friday was portrayed by which actor?", "correct_answer": "Ed ONeil", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed Burrows", "Ed Burns", "Ed Norton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "1973 Pink Floyd album,entitled Dark Side of _____.", "correct_answer": "... the Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["... the Sun", "... Darkness.", "... Parapsychology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first stealth fighter used by the United States Military?", "correct_answer": "F-22 Raptor", "incorrect_answers": ["F/A18 Super Hornet", "F-5 Tiger", "P-47 Thunderbolt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The water cycle is the continuous movement of water above and below the surface of the planet. What is this process also known as?", "correct_answer": "Hydrologic cycle", "incorrect_answers": ["Hydroscopic cycle", "Hydrographic cycle", "Hydrodynamic cycle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Strange as it may be, there are paintings, depicting a blonde one of her.", "correct_answer": "Cleopatra", "incorrect_answers": ["Madamme Butterfly", "Beyonce", "Aretha Franklyn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these gods from different mythologies was not a sun god?", "correct_answer": "Thor", "incorrect_answers": ["Helios", "Sol", "Ra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a type of punch. In a big bowl pour the following ingredients: 1 bottle red wine, shotglass of lime juice, 2 shots Bacardi and add random fruit. Chill the mixture overnight.", "correct_answer": "Sangria", "incorrect_answers": ["Godfather", "Greyhound", "Gin Buck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed Batman in the 2008 movie The Dark Knight, one of the highest-grossing movies of all time?", "correct_answer": "Christian Bale", "incorrect_answers": ["Heath Ledger", "George Clooney", "Val Kilmer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Das Boot is a 1981 film which realistically depicts the harsh life on a what?", "correct_answer": "Fighter submarine", "incorrect_answers": ["Aircraft Carrier", "Overseas military base", "Deserted Island"]}]